page2rss.com 2016-03-06

# Page2RSS Privacy Policy

Page2RSS may collect personal information, including email adresses, when individuals register to use the Page2RSS website and services, submit comments or questions. Like most internet services, our web site automatically receive general information that is contained in our server log files such as your IP address and cookie informaion. These logs are used to generate aggregate reports of website usage. These reports does not contain any personally identifiable information. 

Like many websites, Page2RSS uses cookies to enchance user experience, such as retaining the personal settings. 

Page2RSS uses [web beacons](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Web_beacons) to research certain usage and activities of the Page2RSS web site. The information collected through these web beacons is used to find out more about our users and for more accurate reporting. No personally indetifiable information is collected using these web beacons. 

Page2RSS may use third party tracking services for better understanding of our web site usage. Please refer to [Google Analytics Terms Of Service](http://www.google.com/analytics/tos.html). 

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please refer to [Network Advertising Initiative](http://www.networkadvertising.org/) website. 

Specifically, Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this website. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to you based on your visit to this website and other websites on the Internet. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookies by visiting the Google ad and content network [privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

No information collected by Page2RSS is released to anyone unless we legally required to do so. We do not sell email addresses to anyone. 

Page2RSS reserves the right to modify all or some of this Privacy Policy at any time without notice. If we change our Privacy Policy, we will post the updated document on our web site. 

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this web site you can send an e-mail to [privacy@page2rss.com](mailto:privacy@page2rss.com)
